<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: ferramentas | SEISXIS dot com]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.seisxis.com/blog/categories/ferramentas/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.seisxis.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-05-30T23:18:59-03:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.seisxis.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Junior Andrade]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ferramentas do desenvolvedor moderno: Python LiveReload]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.seisxis.com/blog/2012/05/30/ferramentas-do-desenvolvedor-moderno-python-livereload/"/>
    <updated>2012-05-30T22:22:00-03:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.seisxis.com/blog/2012/05/30/ferramentas-do-desenvolvedor-moderno-python-livereload</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>For about four years I’ve been using Textmate almost every day. I’m very fast with it. I’ve always thought about switching over to VIM or Emacs but I have been scared of losing my speed. In fact, I’ve actually tried Emacs in the past and also wrote a blog post on my experience. I liked it in general, but I ended up coming back to Textmate after a week. Why? I didn’t really feel like I was gaining anything.</p>

<p>So, why would I even consider switching over to VIM?</p>

<p>Server-Side SSH Editor
Split Windows
CTags
Large Development Community &amp; Support
Mastering VIM will lead to greater overall efficiency, given the limited potential of Textmate.
What do I mean by the last item? If you master VIM and its “special” commands, you can be shockingly more efficient than what Textmate allows. The main reason being VIM’s movement commands and VIM-only plugins.</p>

<p>I feel like I’m as fast as I’m going to get in Textmate, but I want to be faster. I also really want to leverage some powerful plugins that the VIM community has created for development, and I also really want to leverage the power of split windows.</p>

<p>One use case for split windows that absolutely strikes my fancy is being able to see a front-end .haml file and also see the appropriate .scss file at the same time. Ooh, just the thought gives me a bout of excitement.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
